{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Architects","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"__cache./api/resource/task/40024/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40024,"taskName":"Architect","taskDescription":"Hire an Architect to Design a Project","xmTaskDescriptor":"Architects","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":9,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Architect Engineer house design build","textMessagingName":"Architect","rolloverLongDesc":"Architects generally have to go through extensive training, certification \u0026 licensing.  They may work on a project basis or on an hourly basis.","rolloverShortDesc":"Credentialed architect to design structure or remodel.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Hire an Architect to Design a Project.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Residential Architects \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e - HomeAdvisor","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":5,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Architect","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Architect","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Architect Need","urlName":"Architect","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best House Architects - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Architect,Engineer,house,design,build,luxury,custom,local,firm,modern,drawings,contemporary,green,architecture,rendering,structural,floorplan,floor,plan","emcCategoryOid":-12005,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":348,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40024/":{"taskOID":40024,"originalTaskOID":40024,"setID":348,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7253,"questionDisplayText":"Project Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes this architectural project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11431,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New structure","answerDisplayText":"New structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11432,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Addition (one story)","answerDisplayText":"Addition (one story)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11433,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Interior remodel of a few rooms","answerDisplayText":"Interior remodel of a few rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11434,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Addition (two or more stories)","answerDisplayText":"Addition (two or more stories)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11435,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Complete remodel (with or without addition)","answerDisplayText":"Complete remodel (with or without addition)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7254,"questionDisplayText":"Building Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of building is involved?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11436,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"House","answerDisplayText":"House","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11437,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Commercial office","answerDisplayText":"Commercial office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11438,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Residential outbuilding (garage, etc)","answerDisplayText":"Residential outbuilding (garage, etc)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11439,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Restaurant","answerDisplayText":"Restaurant","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11440,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Retail store","answerDisplayText":"Retail store","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11441,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Condominium, apartment or town house","answerDisplayText":"Condominum, apartment or town house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7255,"questionDisplayText":"Needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What architectural services do you need? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11442,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Design drawings","answerDisplayText":"Design drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11443,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Technical construction documents","answerDisplayText":"Technical construction documents","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Project evaluation","answerDisplayText":"Project evaluation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11445,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Assist with contractor selection","answerDisplayText":"Assist with selection of general contractor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11446,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Review construction","answerDisplayText":"Review construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11447,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11448,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Permit assistance","answerDisplayText":"Permit assistance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7256,"questionDisplayText":"Approx. Budget (Fees + Construction)","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the approximate total budget for the job (including both architect fees and construction)?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11449,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"$10,000-$25,000","answerDisplayText":"$10,000-$25,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11450,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"$25,001-$50,000","answerDisplayText":"$25,001-$50,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11451,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"$50,001-$100,000","answerDisplayText":"$50,001-$100,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11452,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"$100,001-$200,000","answerDisplayText":"$100,001-$200,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11453,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"$200,001-$300,000","answerDisplayText":"$200,001-$300,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11454,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"$300,001-$500,000","answerDisplayText":"$300,001-$500,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11455,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"$500,001-$1,000,000","answerDisplayText":"$500,001-$1,000,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11456,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Over $1,000,000","answerDisplayText":"Over $1,000,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7257,"questionDisplayText":"Approx. Square footage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the approximate square footage of your project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11457,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 500 square feet ","answerDisplayText":"Less than 500 square feet ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11458,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"500 - 1000 square feet ","answerDisplayText":"500 - 1000 square feet ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11459,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1001 - 2000 square feet ","answerDisplayText":"1001 - 2000 square feet ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11460,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"2001 - 3000 square feet ","answerDisplayText":"2001 - 3000 square feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11461,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Over 3000 square feet ","answerDisplayText":"Over 3000 square feet ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7253,"questionDisplayText":"Project Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes this architectural project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11431,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New structure","answerDisplayText":"New structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11432,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Addition (one story)","answerDisplayText":"Addition (one story)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11433,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Interior remodel of a few rooms","answerDisplayText":"Interior remodel of a few rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11434,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Addition (two or more stories)","answerDisplayText":"Addition (two or more stories)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11435,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Complete remodel (with or without addition)","answerDisplayText":"Complete remodel (with or without addition)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11431,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New structure","answerDisplayText":"New structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11432,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Addition (one story)","answerDisplayText":"Addition (one story)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11433,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Interior remodel of a few rooms","answerDisplayText":"Interior remodel of a few rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11434,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Addition (two or more stories)","answerDisplayText":"Addition (two or more stories)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11435,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Complete remodel (with or without addition)","answerDisplayText":"Complete remodel (with or without addition)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7254,"questionDisplayText":"Building Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of building is involved?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11436,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"House","answerDisplayText":"House","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11437,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Commercial office","answerDisplayText":"Commercial office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11438,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Residential outbuilding (garage, etc)","answerDisplayText":"Residential outbuilding (garage, etc)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11439,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Restaurant","answerDisplayText":"Restaurant","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11440,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Retail store","answerDisplayText":"Retail store","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11441,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Condominium, apartment or town house","answerDisplayText":"Condominum, apartment or town house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11436,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"House","answerDisplayText":"House","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11437,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Commercial office","answerDisplayText":"Commercial office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11438,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Residential outbuilding (garage, etc)","answerDisplayText":"Residential outbuilding (garage, etc)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11439,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Restaurant","answerDisplayText":"Restaurant","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11440,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Retail store","answerDisplayText":"Retail store","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11441,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Condominium, apartment or town house","answerDisplayText":"Condominum, apartment or town house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7255,"questionDisplayText":"Needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What architectural services do you need? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11442,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Design drawings","answerDisplayText":"Design drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11443,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Technical construction documents","answerDisplayText":"Technical construction documents","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Project evaluation","answerDisplayText":"Project evaluation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11445,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Assist with contractor selection","answerDisplayText":"Assist with selection of general contractor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11446,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Review construction","answerDisplayText":"Review construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11447,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11448,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Permit assistance","answerDisplayText":"Permit assistance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11442,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Design drawings","answerDisplayText":"Design drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11443,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Technical construction documents","answerDisplayText":"Technical construction documents","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Project evaluation","answerDisplayText":"Project evaluation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11445,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Assist with contractor selection","answerDisplayText":"Assist with selection of general contractor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11446,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Review construction","answerDisplayText":"Review construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11447,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11448,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Permit assistance","answerDisplayText":"Permit assistance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7256,"questionDisplayText":"Approx. Budget (Fees + Construction)","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the approximate total budget for the job (including both architect fees and construction)?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11449,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"$10,000-$25,000","answerDisplayText":"$10,000-$25,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11450,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"$25,001-$50,000","answerDisplayText":"$25,001-$50,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11451,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"$50,001-$100,000","answerDisplayText":"$50,001-$100,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11452,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"$100,001-$200,000","answerDisplayText":"$100,001-$200,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11453,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"$200,001-$300,000","answerDisplayText":"$200,001-$300,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11454,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"$300,001-$500,000","answerDisplayText":"$300,001-$500,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11455,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"$500,001-$1,000,000","answerDisplayText":"$500,001-$1,000,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11456,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Over $1,000,000","answerDisplayText":"Over $1,000,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11449,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"$10,000-$25,000","answerDisplayText":"$10,000-$25,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11450,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"$25,001-$50,000","answerDisplayText":"$25,001-$50,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11451,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"$50,001-$100,000","answerDisplayText":"$50,001-$100,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11452,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"$100,001-$200,000","answerDisplayText":"$100,001-$200,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11453,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"$200,001-$300,000","answerDisplayText":"$200,001-$300,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11454,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"$300,001-$500,000","answerDisplayText":"$300,001-$500,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11455,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"$500,001-$1,000,000","answerDisplayText":"$500,001-$1,000,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11456,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Over $1,000,000","answerDisplayText":"Over $1,000,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7257,"questionDisplayText":"Approx. Square footage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the approximate square footage of your project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11457,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 500 square feet ","answerDisplayText":"Less than 500 square feet ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11458,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"500 - 1000 square feet ","answerDisplayText":"500 - 1000 square feet ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11459,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1001 - 2000 square feet ","answerDisplayText":"1001 - 2000 square feet ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11460,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"2001 - 3000 square feet ","answerDisplayText":"2001 - 3000 square feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11461,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Over 3000 square feet ","answerDisplayText":"Over 3000 square feet ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11457,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 500 square feet ","answerDisplayText":"Less than 500 square feet ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11458,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"500 - 1000 square feet ","answerDisplayText":"500 - 1000 square feet ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11459,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1001 - 2000 square feet ","answerDisplayText":"1001 - 2000 square feet ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11460,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"2001 - 3000 square feet ","answerDisplayText":"2001 - 3000 square feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11461,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Over 3000 square feet ","answerDisplayText":"Over 3000 square feet ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}